automatedprofitpackage.com 2010-04-16

# Terms And Conditions

**Privacy Policy**  
15 April 2010 

This privacy policy sets out how we will process and use any personal data that you provide to us, or that we may collect as a result of visiting this website. Please read the following information to understand our practices with regards to your personal data and how we will treat it. 

**INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

We may collect and process the following data about you: 

  * Any information that you provide by filling in forms on our site. This includes provided information at the time of registering to use our site, posting material, requesting further services or subscribing to any service offered by us on the site. We might also request further information and if you should report a problem with our site. 

  * We may keep a record of any correspondence if you should contact us. 

  * Details of the resources you access and of your visits to our site 

  * Details of transactions you may carry out through our site and of the completion of your orders. 

**IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES**

We may collect information about your computer; this is statistical data concerning your browsing actions and does not identify you individually. This information includes your IP address where available, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report collective information to our advertisers. 

We may also collect information about your general internet usage using cookie files stored on the hard drive of all computers. The cookies contain valuable information that is transferred to your computers hard drive. In collecting this information we are able to improve our site and deliver a better and more personalised service. 

You can refuse to accept cookies but note that in doing this you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. You can do this by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting. 

Our advertisers may also use cookies but please note that we have no control over this.

**USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION**

We use the information held about you in the following ways: 

  * To notify you of any changes to our service. 

  * To ensure that the content of our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer. 

  * Where you have consented to be contacted, to provide you with the information, products and services requested from us or in the event that we feel will be of interest to you. 

  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, should you choose to do so. 

  * In allowing ourselves to carry out our obligations concerning any contracts entered into between you and us. 

We may also use your data to inform you and provide information on goods and services that may be of interest to you. We may also permit selected third parties to use your data for the same reason.

If you do not want your data used in this way or passed onto third parties for marketing purposes please email support@automatedprofitpackage.com. Please allow 7-10 days for your account to be updated. 

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may disclose your personal information to third parties: 

  * To the prospective buyer or seller of any business or assets in the event that we sell or buy. 

  * If we are under a duty to comply with any legal obligation to disclose or share your personal data. To protect the rights, property and safety of our customers or others, or to enforce our terms of use for the site. For the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction this may include exchanging information with other companies and organisations. 

**THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

From time to time our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you visit any of these sites please note that they have their own privacy policies and you should check these before submitting any personal data. We cannot accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. 

**USE OF DATA COLLECTED**

We use your personal, demographic and profile data to enhance your experience at our site and to enable us to present content we think you might be interested in. We use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners. We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data to improve our site, for statistical analysis, for marketing and promotional purposes, send SMS alerts or notification, and for editorial or feedback purposes for our advertisers. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future telemarketing, SMS text-messaging, e-mails or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online. By using this site, you agree that you may be contacted in any manner contemplated in this section even if your number is found on a do not call registry, in-house list or similar registry. 

**SMS OFFERING AND OPT-OUT RIGHTS**

By completing or submitting a registration form or partial registration form you are consenting to receive SMS, wireless or other mobile offering to your cell phone. You understand that your wireless carrier's standard charges and rates apply to these messages. For SMS text messages, you may remove your information by replying "STOP", "END", or "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received and we will remove your personal information within 10 days of receiving such request. 

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

This policy may change from time to time. Please visit this page for changes. 

**CONTACT**

Automated Website Profits  
support@automatedprofitpackage.com
